It seems that even after getting ready like a Gopi in Vrindavan,
I will not be able to see Kanha ji.
So brother, you left home
for Jaipur but where did you reach?  Straight to Vrindavan
with our group because the wish we had made has been
fulfilled, hence we are going to
visit Prem Mandir.  So let's get
ready to become Gopi.
For which I have this white skirt, a
simple pink blouse and this dupatta which
I have styled like this.  Now let me
wear my family heirloom ₹150 necklace
and these golden earrings.  I had already
applied my makeup, I was just confused, so
I went to my bangle shop and
wore a mix of pink and multi-colour and
we came in such a hurry that we forgot to bring the pin,
so my friend Varsha is stitching it.
Oh my God, sometimes you should
also get the stitches done.  Now I am ready and so is my
group but oh these glass bangles, let us
not be late because we are already
leaving the room at 8:00.  It seems that
Ladli Mandir will be closed.  But if I am
lucky enough to see Lord Krishna,
how can I stay behind?  I did
not ask for anything but I got so engrossed in saying thank you
that Budhudev got confused.   Should I
ask for something or let it be?  It seems that
Mota Bhai has also secretly asked for something.
Now you all also quickly visit the temple
and ask for something.  Your day will be auspicious.
Radhe Radhe.